<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>JecsTools</name>
  <author>jecrell</author>
  <packageId>jecrell.jecstools</packageId>
  <url>https://discord.gg/AaVFA7V</url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.0</li>
    <li>1.1</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependenciesByVersion>
    <v1.1>
      <li>
        <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
        <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
        <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
        <downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
      </li>
    </v1.1>
  </modDependenciesByVersion>
  <description>1.1.1.2 (03-29-2020)

Adds modding components to RimWorld: vehicles, spell casting, weapon slots, oversized weapons, and more!

Note to players: This mod will not change your game, but rather it lets modders do more, so you can have an even more amazing RimWorld experience.

Note to modders: This mod is filled with lots of tools that allow you to do many new and different things in RimWorld. Check out RoxxPloxx's guide for more info here: https://github.com/roxxploxx/RimWorldModGuide/wiki

Partial list of components:

CompAbilityUser
 - Adds spell/ability casting to humanlikes.

CompActivatableEffect
 - Adds an activation graphic for weapons (e.g. lightsaber beam).

CompDeflector
 - Allows the ability to knock projectiles to melee weapons.

CompExtraSounds
 - Allows extra melee sounds to weapons.

CompLumbering
 - Makes a staggered walking animation. (e.g. ATST walking effect)

CompOversizedWeapon
 - Allows weapons with graphic sizes that can be bigger than RimWorld's limits.

CompSlotLoadable
 - Adds slots to objects that can be filled to have effects. (e.g. different ammo types for guns, crystals for lightsabers)

CompToggleDef (by Roxxploxx)
- Allows for something to despawn, change its def, and respawn.

CompVehicle (Experimental)
 - Allows for a pawn to be treated as a vehicle that can be loaded with pilots, gunners, crew, and passengers.

CompInstalledPart (WIP)
- Allows installation and uninstallation of things onto other things. This is particularly useful for weapons on vehicles.

JecsTools.PatchOperationModLoaded
- Allows modders to use xpath code to check if a mod is loaded before patching code.

Additions by ChJees
Additions by roxxploxx
Additions by Swenzi
Additions and transpilers by Erdelf
Extensive hours of testing, debugging, and fixes by Xen.
"Hey, should we make this into a public toolset for people to take advantage of all this cool stuff?" - Jecrell
"Hell yes - this is awesome stuff - people will love it!" - Xen

Thank you to my Patrons for supporting me in my efforts. Without you, none of this would be possible.

These are the most excellent rim dwellers who support me: 
Cade Perkinson, Jay Sacane, John Pahl, Tankok1998 also known as the Shermanlover, Vahl Kilmer, Zsolt Biró, Genaeve, JD2.0, Olteanu Laurentiu, Penelope Charli Whitman, Charlie Garnham, Steven Pretswell, Sultan Saltlick, RainerWingel, Daniel Paseka, Kyben, Charles Morris, Chris Seieroe, Robin Gleeson, Lea Stannard, Teres, David Silberstein, Kiya Nicoll, Matt Harris, Paul Fenwick, Michael Whitehead, Robert Alessi, Elodie, Gothi, Audrin Navarro, Михаил Юрченко, Calum, Tim Stillson, Populous25, Don Homer, Adam Bliss, Maaxar, Christopher, TinyFloatingTurtle, John Kanady, Midgeman, Nathan Getman, Sharp Spook, LionsFate, Cristina Shaver, Mark, George Chong Chuang Ming, Oliver White, roxxploxx, Emily Shaw, Justin Andres, Robin Hager, Kevin Reagan, Austin Harbert, Marcus Regan, E_T, Alex Mederer, Alexander, Toss Antilles

========================
Changelog
========================
1.1.1.2 (03-29-2020)
========================
Activatable weapons now activate in defense thanks to code from qadsad.

1.1.1.1 (03-20-2020)
========================
Fixed issues with damage soak and extra damages. Extra damage should now be dealt properly and damage soak should now deflect damage properly.

1.1.1.0 (03-15-2020)
========================
AbilityUser should now report when line of sight failure takes place for abilities. Extra damages no longer gives errors in combat logs.

1.1.0.20 (03-07-2020)
========================
DefModExtension_ExtraSounds is now processed in the CompExtraSounds Harmony patch. Different pawns with DefModExtension_ExtraSounds in their PawnKindDef can make extra on-hit attack sounds.

1.1.0.19 (02-29-2020)
========================
Hotfix for adding compatibility between the newest version of RimWorld and the previous version of 1.0.

1.1.0.18 (02-29-2020)
========================
Added cross compatibility for RimWorld 1.0 as well as RimWorld 1.1.

1.1.0.17 (02-29-2020)
========================
Updates JecsTools for use in RimWorld 1.1

1.1.0.16 (11-16-2019)
========================
Adds in various work-in-progress code changes. Adds a belated Japanese translation update from Proxyer. Adds a force user code fix from Mehni. Adds BigBox - a solution for larger selection boxes for oversized pawns (such as dragons).

1.1.0.15 (12-14-2018)
========================
Removes apparel detour and replaces it with a harmony patch (thanks to Mehni)

1.1.0.14 (11-18-2018)
========================
Added AlienRace BackstoryDef functionality into the JecsTools namespace

1.1.0.14 (11-18-2018)
========================
Added erdelfs BackstoryDef functionality from AlienRaces to JecsTools.

1.1.0.13 (11-03-2018)
========================
Removed unneeded assemblies from source. Properly includes ThinkNode.dll in the correct location for public usage.

1.1.0.12 (11-03-2018)
========================
Adds ThinkNode_ConditionalWorkTypeDefs, ThinkNodes.JobGiver_Capture, JobGiver_GoToClosestThingDef, ThinkNode_ConditionalHediff, ThinkNodes.ThinkNode_ConditionalHunter, ThinkNode_ConditionalDelay, ThinkNode_ConditionalMissingHuntingWeapon by AliceCecil

1.1.0.11 (10-29-2018)
========================
CompProperties_AnimatedOver added by AliceCecil to draw on top of existing ThingDefs.

1.1.0.10 (10-28-2018)
========================
AliceCecil has adjusted the CompAnimated code to support buildings and other objects (ThingWithComps).

1.1.0.9 (10-19-2018)
========================
Added a try and catch to the ProjectileExtension Harmony patch for CanHitCellFromCellIgnoringRange. This should allow for proper ability casting again.

1.1.0.8 (10-18-2018)
========================
Changed very few issues to allow for the update for RimWorld 1.0.

1.1.0.7 (10-02-2018)
========================
The wall placeworker now also allows other types of walls.

1.1.0.6 (09-30-2018)
===================
Adds new BuildingExtension class to allow for bypasses to SpawningWipes. Perfect for adding furniture on top of existing tables.

</description>
</ModMetaData>